EZEQUIEL CASTELLANOS

FRONT-END Developer



+54 9 387 5432979

🛕 Salta, Argentina

github.com/EzequielCaste

TECHNOLOGIES & SKILLS

- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- React, Next.js
- Styled-Components, Tailwind CSS
- Node.js, MongoDB, Express
- Git and GitHub
- Figma
- Teamwork
- Collaboration and Contributing
- Clear communication

PROJECTS

React Movie App

https://cmyk-tiger.netlify.app/

- Shows movie recommendations fetching data from the TheMovieDB.org API
- Group project which helped us implement version control with Git and GitHub
- Developed with React, React Router and Material UI

Portfolio Website

http://ezecastellanos.com.ar

- Built using Next.js and Tailwind CSS
- Responsive design for small and large screens

ABOUT ME

Front-End developer and English/Spanish translator with previous experience working in group projects for open-source IT communities. I enjoy creating applications and websites that are accessible and interactive. I aim to learn and improve my skills on the latest web technologies and challenge myself every day to learn something new and become a more effective developer.

EXPERIENCE

React Developer

WIP-IT | Oct. 2021 - Mar. 2022

I have worked as a front-end developer for a startup company that developed an application that is used by recruiters across various countries.

My main responsibilities included developing and testing new features for the application and their time estimation. Most of them were related to the UI of the app.

Freelance Web Developer

AO COPIERS | Dec. 2020 - Apr. 2021

I built and maintain the company website implementing responsive design for mobile and tablet.

Volunteer Translator

FREECODECAMP | Feb. 2021 - Present

I contributed to the open-source community with translations of technical articles, proofreading, and correction of articles.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

freeCodeCamp

Mar. 2019 - Mar. 2020

Completed 5 Certifications:

- Responsive Web Design (300 hours)
- Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures (300 hours)
- Front End Libraries (300 hours)
- Data Visualization (300 hours)
- APIs and Microservices (300 hours)

Udemy

Jun. 2020 - Oct. 2020

React: From zero to expert (Hooks and MERN) by Fernando Herrera

Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021